Furukuchi!
Rolling...
Tendi!
Nice one, Nichinoya!
You're in the way!
Nice one, Tanaka!
What was that?!
You're in the way, and our back players can't move up.
Huh?
What? Is... is that actually true?
Not sure. Everybody was so scattered on that play, I really couldn't tell you.
Oh, okay!
I totally did not notice that! Wow!
Kageyama saw it during the play, and Nichinoya knew exactly what he was talking about once it was pointed out.
What impresses me is he thinks he can talk to Nichinoya like that!
Still, you didn't have to say it the way you did!
Alright, why don't you tell me how I should have said it?
What the hell did you just say to me?!
Alright! I'm gonna go ahead and stop you right there.
Sorry about that.
I mean, complaining about Nichinoya is one thing, but complaining about him in the middle of a game like that has gotta be a first.
Well, that's Kageyama for you.
I don't know why, but somehow he seems...
...scarier than usual.
...
抜かしていればいい 傷を恐れ羽ばたかる人生なんて悪性と変わらない 人は一生夢と感動くらい生きてく 痛いくらい羽の腎臓 鳥肌が止まらない 命が熱く燃えている
限界の先 その先で戦う喜びは 勝ち負けすらもどこか遠く 時を止めたこの一瞬が スローモーションで煌めく
さあ暴れな
技を強いに過労しかて 彼は想しみない
Just one touch
ってるからです
頑張って troupeを games色々 牧場でカラズノの好き
が中 AFPは愛して高さを 成功し上げて粘着大な
Damn it that should have been a good one
It's the same as always
What's your deal? We got the point, right? If you have something to say say it
Yeah, right if he told you what to do you'd start pushing back
I mean if you really think Kageyama knows how to accurately express his thoughts, then you've totally lost your damn mind
Yeah, no kidding
But still it's not new for him to be overly critical or to say things in the meanest way possible
So it's weird that he's not doing that
Dang he's a freaking robot a guy can barely keep his balance in that position, but he sends the ball to the perfect spot
Not too high or too low not too close or too far. How much has this guy practiced?
I'm kind of getting emotional
Damn it all sorry guys, no worries
Maybe they're a little too afraid of those blocks
Go go let's go let's go day tech
Yeah
Don't mind us. We're just here to cheer on our precious junior teammates
We don't want to get in the way or anything, so we'll just go watch from upstairs
Hey you three this isn't your school, you know
That's all right. We don't mind
I'm sorry about this
Hey, hey, you guys better not lose today
Show them what date tech tradition is all about
Go go let's go let's go date tech
Thanks, we'll do our best
Well, they must have a lot of free time on their hands
What was that, Futakuchi? We can hear you, you know
Come on, let me hear you guys out here
When we get a point, I want you to scream your lungs out
Futakuchi, look at you now all grown up and leading the team
There's more than one way for us to apply some pressure to our opponent
We're gonna break their spirits and we'll do it just enough that the rest don't really notice
If you can't do it in a practice game, you won't be able to do it in a real one
Way to go Futakuchi, you turd
Shut your trap, Kamasaki
Well, if nothing else, I'm glad date tech is having fun today
Ah, sorry
Is it me or is Kurasuno not playing that great?
No doubt, we could actually win this damn thing
Quick
Damn
Nice kill
Hey, Tsukishima, you were supposed to jump again
You had enough time for another one
Uh, I'm pretty sure Tsuki really doesn't need him to point that out right now
Oh, why are we so irritable?
Is His Majesty an ill-humor today?
Huh?
Well, uh
Tsukishima's usually a little better at taking criticism
Guess Kageyama's the exception
Yeah, I don't think that's really the case
Those two just don't get along
Ooh, this is not good
So, should we call timeout?
Not quite yet
They'll sort it out
Taiji!
Out!
Asahi, you're freaking awful today, man
What's going on?
Ah, damn it
Sorry
Your set was just fine
Then score the damn point
Uh-uh
Ah
Hmm
Asahi, you need to stop
Oh, uh, hey, Kageyama, check this out.
There's something I want to...
Just shut up and listen!
The sets I'm giving you are excellent!
You need to start scoring some points!
Look, everyone, we've seen the return of the king.
If your sorry asses ever expect to win anything,
you better learn to adapt to the way I set!
I apologize.
You know, I always wondered, what's wrong with Kageyama being the king?
Is it that he's too self-centered?
Or that he's bossy?
I mean, either way, it doesn't really matter!
If I don't agree with what he says, I just ignore him!
He can be completely right, but well, if he's a dick, no way I'm gonna do it!
I agree with what he said.
Yeah, okay, Tanaka, whatever.
If someone gives you instructions, you're totally gonna follow him.
Just because you're so strict about maintaining team etiquette.
Yeah, true.
Well, I would appreciate it if you were a little more nice about stuff.
See? It doesn't really matter if you're the king or not.
Oh, come on, man!
Isn't being a king supposed to be, like, awesome?
There is no better set than the one that is easy for the spiker to hit.
And it's definitely true that you only find out what that is by communicating.
But, man, I really don't think that means you're not gonna fight sometimes.
Have you considered why you're having trouble responding to Small Fry's request?
Do you even want to put in the effort at all?
Was that last set decent enough for you, punk?
Hmm, I think I could probably hit it a little bit faster.
So a little zippier, maybe?
I can do that.
You're just a goody-two-shoes.
Uh, I'm sorry, Kageyama.
I've been trying to time my hits in a way where they don't match Date Tech's block attempts.
But I still can't quite get it to work against these guys.
Your sets are great, though.
So keep doing what you're doing.
They're probably gonna keep blocking me for a while, so I'll apologize now.
My bad.
And I'm still trying that super-sharp cut shot!
I mean, what better time than practicing against Date Tech?
And you can just deal with it.
I can't promise I will.
Ha ha ha ha!
Fine with me!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
We're starting the second set!
So they're...fighting?
Well, it's not like you fight just because someone told you that you need to have a fight.
I mean, it happens.
If Kageyama's starting to tell the guys what's on his mind, how about if they try telling him?
Kageyama is so extremely talented.
It's possible that the other members of the team haven't quite figured out how to criticize his play yet.
Hey! You're not attacking from the middle end of today!
What's up, Kageyama? You scared or something?
What?!
We need to go down the middle more!
Hinata's right compared to all their other games.
He is going there less.
I guess there is one guy who can call him out on stuff.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Nice save!
Let's try one and a half ball widths.
Ah, son of a...
He didn't make it!
How are they ever going to survive this spring playing the way they are?
Although, I guess it's not like I actually care.
I guess even Kageyama makes mistakes too!
Hey!
Hmm?
I will not baby you.
Oh? Really?
Well, I wasn't exactly expecting you to.
Kageyama does actually try to get along with people sometimes, and it's not like he was saying anything that came totally out of left field.
So, do you think maybe he's still a little bothered by the feud he had when he was in middle school?
He doesn't really seem like the type of person who would get stuck in the past, though.
People are weighed down by different things.
Middle school, or...
His past?
Whatever happened must be a super heavy weight for him.
Yeah, still.
I don't know all the details and whatnot, but one thing's for sure.
Kageyama's gotten to a point where he understands that there's a distinct possibility he might be wrong about certain things.
And that's a fact his middle school teammates probably forced him to realize by hitting him over the head with it.
One touch!
Chance ball, everyone!
He jumped!
Before, Kageyama would adjust to accommodate all of the spikers' quirks.
But now he's setting it out of reach to get the spiker to hit it from higher up.
Oh, man!
Dang, that was up there!
Hmph.
You jumped that time.
Kageyama!
Way to look smug, buddy!
Suki, settle down and remember, keep your mind still!
Kageyama, stop trying to provoke Suki!
Will you shut up, Tadashi?
It's the greatest position there is because you get to be the ruler!
The setter is the team's control tower!
It's the position that gets the most contact with the ball!
It's the greatest position there is because you get to be the ruler!
Come on now, don't act all surprised.
You know I wouldn't forget you said that.
Act like a goody-goody all you want.
Deep down, you'll always be the king.
Prepare yourself!
From this day on, you shall be known as the new king of the cards!
Well, looks like he's lettin' it go.
I'm not good at figuring out people's feelings.
And apparently, I'm not exactly the best with words either.
Yeah, we know that.
This isn't breaking news, you know, but...
I will be the best setter.
Ever.
Yeah, yeah, we know.
It's not like you haven't made that perfectly clear.
Aw, listen to his majesty.
What a good little boy he's being.
Come on!
Tsukishima, do us all a favor and grow up!
That's coming from Hinata!
Someone's still a little mad about earlier, huh?
That's a nice face.
You smell something stinky?
Did you stop confusing things?
It's okay for me to be a goody-two-shoes here.
It's normal not to know what other people are feeling.
I mean, it's important for you to consider it.
But it's not absolutely necessary during a game.
Your jobs are the following things.
To know how the game is going and how your teammates are doing.
Oh, those two are way more in sync now.
Nice kill, Suki!
The longer Date Tech plays against us, the better their blocks get.
If I'd hit the ball from any lower, they would have totally shut me down.
Oh, wow.
Tsukishima's always been a giant.
So I never would have thought of him as hitting the ball low or anything.
But he can hit from even higher than I thought.
That's what I said!
Yeah.
Looks like he hates doing it, though.
Kogane...
Uh, I mean, Date Tech's setter was setting for him.
And he would sometimes hit the ball from way up there.
Oh.
Tsukishima hits the ball really compact or whatever, and it sounds all like fa-bam, you know?
His swing is quick, too.
Well, a middle blocker's job is to attack as quickly as possible.
So I guess a lot of them are probably like that.
Well, a good setter would keep that speed in mind and set the ball lower, too.
But at the camp, Kogane was setting too high a lot of the time.
Sorry!
And when he messed up, I guess Tsukishima just did what he could.
He didn't really have much of a choice.
So he wound up trying to sync up with Kogane instead of settling.
Oh.
He's really paying attention.
Well, all my teammates are growing up.
No doubt.
You gotta give props to Kageyama for pulling it out of him.
But I'm not gonna stand here and let Tsukishima beat me in jumping height.
Yeah, well.
But I meant you, too.
Nice kill!
Keep him coming, I feel great!
No.
Sorry, Tanaka.
But your spikes are starting to get sloppy.
If you're tired, we can bring someone else in to handle your spot.
Yeah, I'm sure Kageyama only said that because he thought he was looking out for me.
I get it.
I do.
But?
You're not subbing me out, dumbass!
And yeah, sure, that last hit was all power and no technique!
Whoa, he admitted it.
I'm so proud.
It's not like Tanaka's totally wiped out, though.
But I do think we should use this to figure out what we would do in these particular situations.
In games, we'd rather sub people out to give ourselves an advantage instead of making up for problems.
Well, all right.
I'll send him fewer balls and keep my eye on him.
If you absolutely have to, could you at least be cool about it?
It's not like you can say,
You're cut off and I'll be all great, thank you!
Be cool?
Well, I can try.
Yo, for me, I actually do announce it.
If I look around and realized I wasn't getting the ball anymore, I think that would probably hurt my feelings.
So sensitive!
I will do my best, but I can't make any promises.
It's okay. You don't have to spoil them.
They're constantly evolving.
That evolution might not always be a good thing for everyone all the time.
But with this group of second and third years, I think they'll be okay.
The third years are always talking about how glad they are we had such strong first years join.
But I bet Kageyama's glad they're here too.
I'm sure.
Nice receive!
Kageyama!
Left side!
Might be a bit close to the net.
Let's try that again.
Sorry.
There's nothing to apologize for, Asahi!
Yeah, it was our job to pick up the slack there.
Right. Sorry.
He's getting yelled at and told not to apologize?
All at the same time.
Tanaka feeling okay?
Yeah, I don't know what the hell he's doing.
Asahi has to be getting more and more confused.
Are we just ignoring the fact that Kageyama's set was off?
Sorry.
I don't know what's going on here, but Kurashino seems off their game.
Let's crush him!
Asahi!
Over here!
Hinata, send it over!
Crap, it's short!
You're going to hear it!
Yeah!
I'm okay.
Give me a sec.
My bad, guys.
Throw the opponent off guard with a killer serve, then finish them off with a block.
It's the perfect serve-block combo!
As of right now, Daytech's only real standout server is their new captain.
But if they ever manage to train up any more good servers, they might just become untouchable.
Well, next year, the team that ends up giving us the most trouble just might be Daytech.
Daytech.
Daytower.
Pressure, that's why I need God. I don't need help.
Egoist, that's why I need God. I don't have a reason.
We are...挑まずにはいられない。 影さえも振り切ってけ。
現状の限界、乗り越えろチャンス。
We are...戦力をかけた。 We are...怯えることない。
We are...隠しへ変われ、高く、高く、高く、
舞い上がれ、味わった敗北のキスは。
Hello!
Next time, Challenger.